<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linguistics on Truthmaker Semantics</title>
    <link>https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linguistics on Truthmaker Semantics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Applications</title>
      <link>https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/applications/</guid>
      <description>Unpublished Two-Dimensional Truthmaker Semantics Hasen Khudairi  Extends the framework of exact truthmaker semantics with the resources of two-dimensional semantics.
 Keywords:  philosophy modality linguistics  Unpublished manuscript https://philarchive.org/archive/KHUTTS-2   The Whole Truth Stephan Krämer  Formulates an account of what it means to give the “whole truth” and formally models it in exact truthmaker semantics.
 Keywords:  philosophy language exact truthmaking linguistics  In: Outstanding Contributions to Logic: Kit Fine, edited by Federico LG Faroldi and Frederik Van De Putte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory</title>
      <link>https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truthmakersemantics.github.io/publications/linguistics/theory/</guid>
      <description>2021 Routley Star and Hyperintensionality Sergei Odintsov and Heinrich Wansing  Compares HYPE to Heyting-Ockam logic. Contains a characterization of HYPE as identical to a modal system introduced by Moisil. From the perspective of truthmaker semantics, these results can be understood as results about (a certain kind of) inexact truthmaker semantics.
 Keywords:  logic modality inexact truthmaking linguistics  In: Journal of Philosophical Logic 50: 33-56 10.1007/s10992-020-09558-5   2020 Logics of Synonymy Levin Hornischer  Surveys various “logics of synonymy,” i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
